export default data = [
  {
    question:
      'India is a federal union comprising twenty-eight states and how many union territories?',
    options: ['6', '7', '8', '9'],
    correct_option: '8',
  },

  {
    question: 'Which of the following is the capital of Arunachal Pradesh?',
    options: ['Itanagar', 'Dispur', 'Imphal', 'Panaji'],
    correct_option: 'Itanagar',
  },
  {
    question: 'What are the major languages spoken in Andhra Pradesh?',
    options: [
      'Odia and Telugu',
      'Telugu and Urdu',
      'Telugu and Kannada',
      'All of the above languages',
    ],
    correct_option: 'Telugu and Urdu',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the state flower of Haryana?',
    options: ['Lotus', 'Rhododendron', 'Golden Shower', 'Not declared'],
    correct_option: 'Lotus',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which of the following states is not located in the North?',
    options: ['Jharkhand','Jammu and Kashmir','Himachal Pradesh','Haryana'

],
    correct_option: 'Jharkhand',
  },
  {
    question:
      ' In which of the following state, the main language is Khasi?',
    options: ['Mizoram','Nagaland','Meghalaya','Tripura'],
    correct_option: 'Meghalaya',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which is the largest coffee-producing state of India?',
    options: [
    'Kerala','Tamil Nadu','Karnataka','Arunachal Pradesh'
    ],
    correct_option: 'Karnataka',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which state has the largest area?',
    options: [
  'Maharashtra','Madhya Pradesh'
,'Uttar Pradesh','Rajasthan'
    ],
    correct_option: 'Rajasthan',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which state has the largest population?',
    options: [
    'Uttar Pradesh','Maharastra','Bihar','Andra Pradesh'
    ],
    correct_option: 'Uttar Pradesh',
  },
  {
    question: 'In what state is Elephant Falls located?',
    options: [
    'Mizoram','Orissa' ,'Manipur','Meghalaya'
    ],
    correct_option: 'Meghalaya',
  }
];
